Guide to the National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets 1945-1969
National Association of Manufactures Pamphlets
- NAM Labor Relations Bulletin, 1939-1942; Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Item 20: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. November 1939. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Labor Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1943. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Industrial Relations Bulletin, Publication (Box 2, Folder 5)
- NAM Press Releases (1 of 2), 1950-1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Management Faces the Pension Problem, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 2: Business Size and the Public Interest, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Settlement of Labor Disputes and Wage Stabilization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 2, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Inflation Is the Only Alternative to Pay-As-We-Go, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: The Meaning of Unemployment Statistics, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Richard R. Bennett. December 4th. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By Richard C. Bennett. December 6, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 6, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 10: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 11: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 12: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 13: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 14: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 7, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 16: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 17: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 18: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 19: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 20: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 21: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 22: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 23: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 24: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 25: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 8, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 27: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 28: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 29: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 30: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 31: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 32: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 33: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 34: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 35: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 36: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 37: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 38: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 39: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 9, 1950. Item is in English.
  - Item 40: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 7, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 41: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 42: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 43: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 44: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 45: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 8, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 47: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 48: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 49: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 50: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 51: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 52: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 53: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 54: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 6, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 55: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 56: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 57: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 58: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 59: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 60: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 61: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Item 62: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 4, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 63: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 5, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 64: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 6)
- NAM Press Releases (2 of 2), 1950-1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 2: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 3: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 4: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 5: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 6: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 7: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 8: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 9: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 10: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 12: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 13: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 14: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 15: News from the NAM, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Item 16: Industry's View, Publication (Box 2, Folder 7)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 1, 1951. Item is in English.
- NAM Press Releases, 1949; Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: Effective Communication in Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 2: Employee Communications, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. June 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: 1949 N.A.M. Board of Directors, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 4: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 10, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 6: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 9, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 8: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 9, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 10: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 11: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 12: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 14: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 15: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 16: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 17: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 8, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 20: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 9, 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 24: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 26: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 9 ,1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 27: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 8, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 29: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 34: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 36: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 7, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 39: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 42: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 46: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 47: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 6, 1949. Item is in English.
  - Item 53: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 8)
- NAM Publications, 1947-1969; Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: A New Force for Inflation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Union Monopoly Power, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Your Opportunities in Industry as a Technician, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. April 1957. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Your Opportunities in Science and Engineering, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 5: Do You Still Have the Right to Run Your Plant?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 6: Your Opportunities in Industry as a Skilled Craftsman, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 7: Address and Invocation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Charles Francis Boynton. December 3, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. December 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Presentation to Ross T. McIntire, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
    By Earl Bunting. December 4, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 11: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 12: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Item 13: 58th Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 9)
- NAM Publications, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Challenge to Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Walter B. Weisenburger. January 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Industry Believes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 4: Trends in Industrial Research and Patent Practices, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Item 5: Why Management is Opposed to Industry-Wide Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Walter B. Weisenburger. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Personnel Organization and Administration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Howard Dirks. January 6-10, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Freedom and Prices, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Robert R. Wason. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Industry's Answer to the Police State, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Earl Bunting. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: The NAM's Public Relations Program, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By J. Howard Few. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Building on Faith, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Holcombe Parkes. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Panel- Economic Outlook and What to do About It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Henry Hazlitt. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Panel- Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Alan Temple. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: The Legislative Outlook, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Hon. Joseph W. Martin, Jr. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Panel- Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By William H. Grimes. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Panel- Economic Outlook and What to Do About It, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By H. B. Arthur. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: The Challenge From Abroad, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Allen Welsh Dulles. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: The Fight for Men's Mind, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Robert I. Gannon. December 3, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: The Causes of Industrial Peace, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Clarence Francis. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Effective Leadership for Better Employee Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Chas. J. Stilwell. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Administrering the Labor-Management Relations Act, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Robert N. Denham. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Costs vs. Benefits in Government Spending, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Hon. Harry F. Byrd. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: Benefits Versus Costs in Federal Government Spending, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Hon. John J. Sparkman. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: Call to Action on Taxes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Don G. Mitchell. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 10)
    By Raymond S. Smethurst. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1947; Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. Press Release December 5, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: From NAM Newsroom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 3: Communist Influence in Labor Unions, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By H.W. Story. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Peaceful Settlement of Disputes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Cyrus S. Ching. December 4, 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: New Issues in Collective Bargaining, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Frank Rising. 12/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: An Address by Morris Sayre, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Morris Sayre. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Keeping Our Powder Dry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Thomas J. Hargrave. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Patents and Progress, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Alexander Wiley. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Tailoring the Budget to the Nation's Needs, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Thomas S. Holden. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Capital Needs of an Expanding Economy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Murray Shields. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: The Role of Government in Research, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Gustav Egloff. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Fighting Inflation: A Two-Front Challenge, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Lewis H. Brown. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Industry's Stake in International Issues, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By J.R. Suman. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: What the Public Expects of Management and Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By George W. Taylor. 12/4/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: On Guard For Freedom, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By F.C. Crawford. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Approved By Congress of American Industry, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Let's Stay Free, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By Charles E. Wilson. 12/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: How the New Labor Management Relations Act Affects You, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 19: Preparing to Negotiate, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Organized Labor's Fears Under the Taft-Hartley Act, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 9/5/1947. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Labor-Management Relations Problems, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Item 22: Collective Bargaining A Two-Way Process, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 4/29/1946. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: The Closed Shop, Publication (Box 2, Folder 11)
- NAM Publications, 1959; Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Labor Law Reform, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 2: The Mobilization for Understanding of Private Enterprise, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By H.W. Prentis, Jr. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Our Modern Pioneers and the American Patent System, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. 2/27/1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Production For Use, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By George E. Sokolsky. February 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: War Control of Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 6: Who Is the Consumer?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By George E. Sokolsky. February, 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Who Owns this Country?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 8: Your Town, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By George E. Sokolsky. May 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Living Standards Here and Abroad, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 10: Machines and Progress, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 11: An American Business Man Talks to Youth, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By George E. Sokolsky and C.M. Chester. February 1940. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Industrial Health Advances, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 13: Liberty of the Individual, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 14: Union Power and Labor-Management Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. February 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Statement for the Subcommittee on Labor, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 26, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: 10 Part Program for Better Labor Legislation, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Item 17: Labor-Management Reporting and Disclosure Act of 1959, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 18: Should a Man Have to Join a Union to Work?, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Charles A. Kothe. August 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 19: Labor-Management Relations A Look Ahead, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Charles R. Sligh, Jr. August 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Labor Legislation Summary Analysis of the Kennedy Bill, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. May 15, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Employment Skills for Tomorrow's Economy, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Donald J. Hardenbrook. June 11, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 22: The A,B,C of Preparing for Arbitration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. March 9-13, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 23: This We Believe about Economic Education, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. September 25, 1959. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: How do People Grow in a Business Organization, Publication (Box 2, Folder 12)
    By Moorhead Wright. May 1959. Item is in English.
- NAM Publications, 1951; Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Industry Believes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 2: Human Relations and Efficient Production, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 3: How Our Business System Operates, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 4: The Basic Principles Behind Good Employee Relations, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 5: Compulsory Arbitration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. August 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Studies on Concentration, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By National Association of Manufacturers. July 1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Co-Determination A Report of the Mission to Germany, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 8: Settlement of Labor Disputes, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 9: Paying As We Go, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 10: Inflation is the Only Alternative to Pay-As-We-Go, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 11: Cut Non-Defense Spending Now, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Item 12: Address by Right Reverend Henry K. Sherrill, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Henry K. Sherrill. 12/7/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 13: Your and Your Schools, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)
    By Herold C. Hunt. 12/7/1951. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Research and Development Board, Publication (Box 2, Folder 13)